So, I've been in this studio for about a week.
このスタジオにきて一週間くらいだけど、
But I'm developing a long-term project with them.
彼らとは長期間のプロジェクトをやっているの
Which involves, effectively in short, transplanting an exterior wall in an existing building
そのなかで、効率的に一気に、ブロックを 一つずつ展示会場まで運んで、
from a site yet to be determined, brick by brick, here to the mill.
既存の建築物の外壁を移動させるような事もやるわ どこからか運ぶかはまだ決まって無いんだけど
It just so happened that there's a demolition happening right now down the street from here.
ここからこの道をずっと行ったところで、 まさに今取り壊しが行われている
And I've been observing and documenting the	demolition.
私はその取り壊しをずっと観察して ドキュメントを作っているの
They're doing it all with machines, because it's quite a big building.
建物はとても大きいので、 取り壊しは全て重機で行われている
I've just been asking the guys about, you know, demolition and how to do it,
そこの人たちから、取り壊しについてと、 取り壊しのやりかたについて聞き取りをしているのよ
and it turns out that this company has been responsible for a lot of the demolition in
それでこの会社が、多くの取り壊しに関して、 責任をもっているという事が分かった
Manchester over the last thirty years.
ここ30年間のマンチェスターで行われている 取り壊しに関してね
And I think this is partially why this project as well.
そして私は部分的にだけど、これが このプロジェクトの理由だと思った
They seem to have this policy of trying to create a new future by razing.
彼らは取り壊す事で新しい未来を創造する、 というポリシーを持っているように見える
But it's about the spectacle of change, and they want people to feel like change is happening,
だけどそれはスペクタクル的な変化について言っていて、彼らは 人々には、偶発的な変化のように感じて欲しいと思っている
but they don't actually have any real plans for	what's going to happen to that site yet.
彼らは実際のところ、具体的なプランは何も持ってないの
It's mainly about the internet, I guess.
主にインターネットに関する事だと思う
And the way that you sort of have this kind of divorced relationship from history.
そこでは関係性が歴史から切り離されている
And I was looking at the legacy of the club scene here, which is a bit of a strange thing,
私はここでクラブシーンの現状を見てたの 少し変な事だけど、
and sort of what's happening now in terms of kids who are a generation younger than I am.
今ここの、私より若い世代の子供達に起こっている事をね
And their relationship to things.
また彼らと物事の間の関係の作り方をね
It kind was about this leveling process with me, as someone who's not from here,
これは私にとっての、この土地の出身でないものとして 対等になるためのプロセスなんだけど、
and didn't grow up with it, and has a very, quite different background but sort of similar interests.
この環境で育ってない者として、そして本当に異なった バックグラウンドをもち、けれども同様の興味を持つ者として
I'm kind of excited for how you can access a level playing field, something that happens through
どうしたら対等な立場になれるのか、 ある種エキサイティングな感覚があるわ
the internet that, you know, like maybe me and these kids have an equal access,
インターネットの中に発生するような場所ね 子供でも対等な立場になれる
which is also kind of one that's also very devoid.
そしてその場所は同時に、とても欠落してもいるわ
If it's taking that building and then trying to just, you know, take it out of time,
もしもその作業が、ただそのビルを時間から取り除いて、
and then make a kind of imprint of it somewhere else,
どこか別の場所に刻み込むなら、
but if it is just of bricks then it kind of comes back all apart again.
でも、それがただのブロックで、 またばらばらになってしまうなら、
It's just about carving out a moment, kind of like a photograph almost.
それはただ瞬間を彫刻することであって、 なんというか、ほぼ写真のようなものね